gamekiller.net 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy - GameKiller - Bringing The Pain To Each And Every Game

**What information do we collect?**

When you enter this site, your IP address is automatically collected and we employ the use of cookies (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information) to understand and save your preferences for future visits. . We collect this information from you when you register on our site, place an order for Premium services or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering VIP on our site, as appropriate, you may also be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or phone number in order to confirm that you are the person you claim to be. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• _To improve our website_   
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

• _To process transactions_   
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

• _To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature._

• _To send periodic emails_   
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional mass occasional emails containing news regarding Gamekiller as a whole. 

• _Server administration_   
In the event of a server attack, we log your IP in order to see who is behind such attacks. 

• _Moderating the forums_   
When moderating the forums, we use your IP to be able to differentiate users and see who's who. This is also to enforce our "no multiple accounts" policy. 

• _In the case of a police investigation_   
We reserve the right to give your IP to the corrent authorities in the event that law enforcement requires it for an ongoing investigation. 

• _Third Party Advertising_   
The Google AdSense advertisements do not collect personal information, however, we have no control regarding their collection of things such as IP addresses and such. 

• _Contests/Polls_   
In order to maintain contest integrity and ensure that there are no duplicate entries, we use this information to ensure that each entry is a unique one. 

• _Order Forms_   
We use an order page in order to process donations and Premium subsscription orders. On this page we'll collect personal information regarding confirmation of your identity and for payment purposes.   
While we will never use for information for malicious purposes, we also reserve the right to use your information for purposes we deem to be crucial to the betterment of our forum. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be stored on our servers for identification purposes. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act) and require that all members of this forum be aged at least 13 years or older, unless given the express permission of a parent via an email to mymapleblaze@gmail.com.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. While we do not own any content you post, you give us the permission to do with your information whatever we see fit. In addition to this, Gamekiller is not responsible if you accidentally or if another member releases information to the public. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.GameKiller.net   
mymapleblaze@gmail.com   
Last Updated: August 6th, 2010
